const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Which Star Wars movie was filmed entirely in the studio?',
      answers: [
        'Revenge of the Sith',
        'Attack of the Clones',
        'Return of the Jedi',
        'Star Wars: A New Hope'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Revenge of the Sith'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the three main heroes (Luke, Leia, and Han Solo) in the first Star Wars trilogy refused to sign a three picture deal?',
      answers: [
        'Harrison Ford',
        'Mark Hamill',
        'Carrie Fisher',
        'They All Signed'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Harrison Ford'
    },
    {
      question: 'What color is Mace Windu\'s lightsaber?',
      answers: [
        'Green',
        'Purple',
        'Black',
        'Blue'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Purple'
    },
    {
      question: '"The Star Wars Holiday Special" marked the first appearance of which Star Wars character?',
      answers: [
        'Jabba the Hutt',
        'Boba Fett',
        'Jar Jar Binks',
        'Lando Calrissian'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Boba Fett'
    },
    {
      question: 'What actor pulled out of Episode III: Revenge of the Sith when he discovered that non-union actors were being used in the film?',
      answers: [
        'Mel Gibson',
        'Gary Oldman',
        'George Clooney',
        'Gary Coleman'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Gary Oldman'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the only non Jedi in the original Star Wars trilogy to use a lightsaber?',
      answers: [
        'Chewbacca',
        'R2-D2',
        'Han Solo',
        'Princess Leia'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Han Solo'
    },
    {
      question: 'What character did George Lucas consider casting as a person with dwarfism?',
      answers: [
      'Princess Leia',
      'Jar Jar Binks',
      'Luke Skywalker',
      'Chewbacca'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Luke Skywalker'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who served as Jabba the Hutt\'s chief of staff?',
      answers: [
        'Sarlacc',
        'Nute Gunray',
        'Maz Kanata',
        'Bib Fortuna'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Bib Fortuna'
    },
    {
      question: 'Approximately how many languages can C-3PO speak?',
      answers: [
      '6 Trillion',
      '6 Million',
      '6 Thousand',
      '6 Billion'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '6 Million'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Episode VI: Return of the Jedi, the growls and sounds of the Rancor in Jabba\'s Palace were actually made by what animal?',
      answers: [
        'Panther',
        'Wolverine',
        'Dachsund',
        'Pigeon'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Panther'
    }
];
